- [WHISPERING] Sheldon?
- Shh!
[WHISPERING]
Penny's sleeping.
Are you insane?
You can't break into a woman's apartment
in the middle of the night and clean.
(Sheldon:)I had no choice.
(Sheldon:)I couldn't sleep knowing that just
outside my bedroom was our living room...
...and outside our living room
was that hallway...
(Sheldon:)...and immediately adjacent
to that hallway was this.
Do you realize that if Penny wakes up...
(Leonard:)...there is no reasonable explanation
as to why we're here?
(Sheldon:)I just gave you a reasonable explanation.
(Leonard:)No, no. You gave me an explanation.
(Leonard:)It's reasonableness will be determined
by a jury of your peers.
(Sheldon:)Don't be ridiculous. I have no peers.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, we have to get out of here.
[PENNY SNORING]
(Sheldon:)You might want to speak
in a lower register.